<CALLOUT>
	<GENERAL>
		<CALLOUTMESSAGE><![CDATA[Photography of Police Station]]></CALLOUTMESSAGE>
		<FURTHERINFORMATION><![CDATA[A person is ~y~taking photos of the station~w~, speak with them to find out why.]]></FURTHERINFORMATION>
	</GENERAL>
	<OUTCOME0>
	</OUTCOME0>
	<OUTCOME1>
		<DIALOGUES>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Hi there. What's going on here?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ Nothing. Nothing at all.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Put the camera down, I'd like to speak with-]]></DIALOGUE>
		</DIALOGUES>
	</OUTCOME1>
	<OUTCOME2>
		<DIALOGUES>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ What's up? What's brought you here?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ I'm not doing anything illegal, please leave me be.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ I'm just trying to strike a conversation to understand what's going on.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ And I'm just trying to do things, which are perfectly legal.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ I'd just like to speak with you.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ Don't attempt to infringe my photography rights on public property.]]></DIALOGUE>
		</DIALOGUES>
	</OUTCOME2>
	<OUTCOME3>
		<DIALOGUES>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Hello, can I ask why you are taking photos of the station?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ It was for my social media channel, is that okay?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ It is legal, yes, just rather odd to be doing for so long.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ I understand, I'm done now so I'll move along.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Cheers, thank you.]]></DIALOGUE>
		</DIALOGUES>
	</OUTCOME3>
	<OUTCOME4>
	<NOTIFICATION><![CDATA[Phone number has been received, and the initial investigations have begun. Thank you.]]></NOTIFICATION>
		<DIALOGUES>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Hi, what are you doing taking photos of the station?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ You really want to know?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Yes please, go ahead.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ I realise how stupid I sound saying this, but someone, with the name of Jeff, texted me asking me to.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ Yeh, in hindsight that was a bit of a sketchy thing to do.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ I think we are both thinking the same thing. Can you give me their number?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ I think you ought to go home now, and possibly think about who you are speaking to.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ Yes, I understand. Sorry for the trouble.]]></DIALOGUE>
		</DIALOGUES>
	</OUTCOME4>
		<OUTCOME5>
		<DIALOGUES>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Hi, what are you doing taking photos of the station?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ Hi Officer! I'm a huge fan of emergency services, and the work they do. I've just been taking some photos of your station, is that okay?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ I see, so this is some sort of hobby if I gather correctly?]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ Exactly! I wanted to be a police officer, but being on the other side of the station you can see it didn't go to plan.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ That's interesting to hear, I just wanted to check on you to figure out what was going on.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ I can only apologise for wasting your time, but I've finished up my shots anyway, it looks pretty good if I say so myself.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~b~You:~w~ Not a problem in the slightest, I hope you have a wonderful rest of your day.]]></DIALOGUE>
			<DIALOGUE><![CDATA[~r~Suspect:~w~ Well, off I go then. Maybe we'll cross paths some point in the future.]]></DIALOGUE>
		</DIALOGUES>
	</OUTCOME5>
</CALLOUT>


<!-- <![CDATA[]]> -->